nesn.com 2017-12-26

# Privacy Policy | NESN.com

Thank you for visiting nesn.com, a New England Sports Network LP site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this NESN web site.

**The Information We Collect**

At some NESN web sites, you can enter contests, vote in polls, order products or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that you may submit in these pages can include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At some other NESN web sites, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages can include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some of our web sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site’s activities and offerings.

We also may use software tools to automatically collect certain anonymous, non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the Internet protocol address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet, your general location (such as the city where you are located), the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Opera, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Linux, Mac OS or Microsoft Windows) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, Earthlink). We do not automatically collect geolocation information that would be sufficient to identify your street name or the name of your city or town.

We also may use cookies and web beacons to collect information (as described below).

**Children’s Privacy**

Consistent with the provisions of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), NESN does not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of thirteen (13). The activities on NESN web sites directed to children under 13 or where NESN has actual knowledge that a user is under 13 do not require any personal information to be submitted. NESN web sites directed to children under 13 or where NESN has actual knowledge that a user is under 13 do not require registration and do not collect personal information through features such as contests, polls, product orders, subscriptions or online forums. If, upon notification by a parent or guardian, or discovery by other means, that a child under thirteen (13) has improperly registered on this site by using false information, we will immediately cancel the child’s membership and/or participation and delete the child’s personally identifiable information from our records.

**How We Use the Information that You Provide or We Collect**

We may use the information you provide or that we collect about you online to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, or to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a “letter to our editors”, comments sent to certain personalities, a posting to a blog or a discussion board), we may publish your screen name and other non-personally identifiable information you have provided to us.

By posting messages, uploading files, inputting data, or engaging in any other form of online communication with us, you are granting NESN a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to:

Use, copy, sublicense, adapt, transmit, publicly perform or display any such communication.

Sublicense to third parties the unrestricted right to exercise any of the foregoing rights granted with respect to the communication.

The foregoing grants shall include the right to exploit any proprietary rights in such communication, including but not limited to rights under copyright, trademark, service mark or patent laws under any relevant jurisdiction.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect online to improve the design and content of our web site, protect the security of our web site, and to enable us to personalize your Web experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze web site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our web site and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company.

Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

Certain NESN web sites may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If a web site shares personally identifiable information, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses either at the point of submission of your personally identifiable information or prior to any such disclosure.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this site.

Finally, the NESN web sites covered by this Privacy Policy will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, submitting this information at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the web site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand web site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

“Web beacons” (also referred to as a web bug, tracking bug, tracking pixel, pixel tag, 1×1 gif, or clear gif) are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to track when a web page or e-mail is being read, and from what computer. They can also be used to see if an e-mail was forwarded to someone else or if a web page was copied to another website. We may use web beacons on this web site from time to time for this and other purposes.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on the NESN web sites.

The NESN sites covered by this Privacy Policy sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the web site activity. We have no control over these third parties’ use of this information. The web site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

Some of the NESN sites covered by this Privacy Policy may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information you provide and we collect online.

**How You can Access or Correct Information**

Access to personally identifiable information that is collected from our sites may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of collection.

You may also send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes, please include your first name, last name, e-mail address, and the password you use for said service.

Office of Public Relations  
NESN  
480 Arsenal St. Bldg 1  
Watertown, MA 02472

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the online Privacy Policy for this web site or its implementation you may contact us at online@nesn.com.

**Updates**

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this statement so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

**Third Party Marketing**

This web site does not disclose personally identifiable information to third parties unless notification is provided when the information is submitted and the user does not opt out of such disclosure at that time.

**Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Analytics**

This web site has implemented and uses Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Analytics. This web site uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads and other ads on sites across the Internet. This web site and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to this web site and other web sites.

Visitors to this web site can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Visitors to this web site can also implement the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

NESN does not behaviorally target advertising to children under 13 on sites that are directed to children or where NESN has actual knowledge that a user is under 13.

**Third-Party Ad Servers**

We and our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our web site and to conduct research about the advertisements. Below is a representative list of such third parties and a link to their privacy notices. For more information, click on the links below.

  * Atlas DMT: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or <http://www.atlasdmt.com/privacy/> Advertising.com: <http://www.advertising.com/privacy_policy.php>
  * Bluestreak: <http://www.bluestreak.com/web/aboutus_privacypolicy.htm>
  * DoubleClick: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy>
  * Eyeblaster: <http://www.eyebalster.com/site/privacy_policy_down.htm>
  * EyeWonder: <http://www.eyewonder.com/about/privacy.cfm>
  * Dynamic Logic: <http://www.dynamiclogic.com/privacy_policy.php>
  * Klipmart: <http://www.klipmar.com/privacy.html>
  * Millward Brown IntelliQuest: <http://www.intelliquest.com/privacy/intro.asp>
  * Unicast: [http://www.unicast.com/company/privacy.asp ](http://www.unicast.com/company/privacy.asp%E2%80%A8%E2%80%A8)
